yoursuccessstore.com 2019-07-23

# Privacy Policy

SUCCESS Partners Holding Co. ("SUCCESS," "we," "us" or "our") values its customers and respects their right to privacy. We are committed to protecting our users’ information and to making our users aware of our online practices regarding the privacy of their information. That includes meeting or exceeding requirements under data protection acts and regulations (including the General Data Protection Regulation Act).

By accessing this web site (the “Site”), you expressly consent and agree to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy, including our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree, then please do not use or access our Site.

## **INFORMATION COLLECTED**

Visitors to our Site can access the Site’s home page and browse the Site without disclosing any personally identifiable information. We may track information provided to us by your browser, including the web site you came from (known as the "referring URL"), the type of browser you use, the time and date of access, and other information that does not personally identify you.

SUCCESS may also collect personal information when you provide it to SUCCESS, such as by submitting to the Site content to the Site, requesting e-mail updates and newsletters, reminders for events, special dates or offers, purchasing materials or products, participating in a webinar, responding to a survey or questionnaire from us, or when you provide comments, suggestions and submissions to us via the Site or otherwise. SUCCESS may collect personal information in connection therewith such as your name, address, e-mail address, phone numbers and other relevant information. Depending upon the services you elect to use or receive, we may also collect device-specific information, mobile network information, including your mobile device number or other identifier.

Information we collect from you, when you choose to provide it to us (e.g. when you set up an account with us), may include your name, your mailing address (where you request/purchase certain materials), your email address and other contact information you may provide when purchasing materials or products from our Site. We use a third party provide to process credit card payments; we do not maintain and/or store any credit card information. Please see the privacy policy of that third party when purchasing products or services from our Site.

We may also maintain a record of your online history on the Site, and the aforementioned information in connection therewith.

You also understand that when you post information to our Site, it may be indexable by search engines. If a third party then copies your content posted on our Site, your election to remove that content from our Site may not remove your content from other sources that have since linked to or copied your content.

## How the Information Is Used.

By using this website, you agree that SUCCESS may use the information you give it to provide services to you or provide information, notices and reminders that SUCCESS thinks you may find interesting or useful, or that you specifically requested. We may from time-to-time provide your name and email address to marketing partners. SUCCESS may also use the information for other actions you take or other services you request on our Site.

Your responses to and results from the questionnaires and/or surveys that you may complete are owned by us, and we and others may use them in a variety a ways to enhance our delivery of information and services to you. We may also share results with third parties, including market research firms, but in so doing, we will not include your personal information. Instead, results will be aggregated (for example, by age range, geographic region, etc.).

We may also use information we collect from you to:

  * perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our features, including your submission of content for our Site, services or content, or products, services or content offered by others, including our participating affiliates and vendors;
  * communicate with you by e-mail, postal mail, facsimile, telephone and/or mobile devices about products and services that may be of interest to you, and/or about content that you have submitted to the Site;
  * develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our Site and other web sites;
  * use your email to communicate with you if you forget your password;
  * enforce our terms and conditions;
  * manage our business; and
  * perform functions in connection with providing information and services to you, including without limitation, reviewing and posting your content to the Site.

We may receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.

Please note that information, images, and other materials you post or submit for posting to the Site is not protected by this Privacy Policy and may be shared with third parties by us.

Accordingly you should not submit to SUCCESS any information that you do not want shared with others. Further you will not submit any information or content regarding a third party unless you are expressly authorized to do so.

## Personal Information of Minors.

SUCCESS does not knowingly solicit or collect personally identifiable information online from minors. If SUCCESS learns that a minor has submitted personally identifiable information online, in contravention of these measures, it will take all reasonable measures to delete such information from its databases and to not use such information for any purpose (except where necessary to protect the safety of the minor or others as required by law).  
Links.

The Site may provide links to other web sites that SUCCESS thinks you will find interesting or useful. SUCCESS is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites.

## External Distribution of Personally Identifiable Information and of Confidential Information.

SUCCESS owns several Sites, all of which are owned directly, or through affiliated companies of SUCCESS. In some instances, we may share your personal information within the SUCCESS organization to provide, maintain and improve our products and services.

SUCCESS does not externally distribute personally-identifiable information of a user of the Site, except if a user specifically opts-in that certain of its personally-identifiable information be distributed to a third party, or if necessary to protect the rights of SUCCESS or others. External distribution does not include certain limited distributions such as sharing personally-identifiable information with a third party working on behalf of SUCCESS, transfer of personally-identifiable information in connection with the sale of SUCCESS’s assets or the merger of SUCCESS or the disclosure of personally-identifiable information in connection with legal proceedings, investigations of crimes, or other governmental investigations. Transferring personally-identifiable information in connection with a sale or merger and sharing personally-identifiable information with an entity or person working on behalf of SUCCESS is considered an onward transfer to third parties and is permitted under this policy.

## Third-Party Service Providers.

We may employ other companies and individuals, including third party metrics and analytic tools, to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), and providing customer service. These service providers have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but such service providers are not authorized to use personal information for other purposes.

## Use of Your Information to Protect SUCCESS and Others.

We may release your personal information if we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our [Terms of Use](https://privacy.www.success.com/terms-of-use/); or to protect the rights, property, or safety of SUCCESS, our other users, or third parties. This includes exchanging information with other companies and entities for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. We do not, however, sell, rent, share, or otherwise disclose personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Policy.

## Use of Cookies.

Please see our detailed [cookies policy here](http://www.success.com/cookie-policy).

## Third Party Advertisers.

We may use outside companies to display ads on our Site, including manufacturers of the products we offer on the Site, and third parties acting on their behalf. These ads and notices may contain cookies. Third parties also may post content to our Site. These postings may also contain cookies.

## How Long We Keep Your Personally-Identifiable Information.

SUCCESS retains the personally-identifiable information you provide to us as reasonably necessary in connection with SUCCESS’ operation of its business and for you to use the Site, or for us to provide customer support or other services described herein in connection with the Site.  
Security.

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow reasonable standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

ALTHOUGH SUCCESS USES REASONABLE SECURITY PRECAUTIONS WITH RESPECT TO YOUR PERSONALLY-IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM AND STORED ON OUR SERVERS, SUCCESS CANNOT GUARANTEE THAT ANY OF YOUR PERSONALLY-IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION STORED ON OUR SERVERS, OR TRANSMITTED TO OR FROM THE SITE, WILL BE FREE FROM UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT NOT PROHIBITED BY LAW, SUCCESS DISCLAIMS AND SHALL HAVE NO LIABILITY FOR ANY LOSS OF, UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS OR DAMAGE TO, OR INTERCEPTION OF ANY OF YOUR PERSONALLY-IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION BEING STORED ON OUR SERVERS OR ON THE SITE, OR TRANSMITTED TO OR FROM THE SITE OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SERVICES.

## Access; Review and Correction.

Customers can, by emailing SUCCESS at [admin@successpartners.com](mailto:admin@successpartners.com) review and correct the personally identifiable information that has been collected from them by SUCCESS.

## Opt-Out.

At any time should you wish for us to no longer communicate with you, or wish to have us delete or destroy any names, email addresses, content or communications you send to us, please write to us at: SUCCESS, 5800 Democracy Drive, Plano Texas 75024, or email us at [admin@successpartners.com](mailto:admin@successpartners.com).  However, then you may no longer be able to use the Site and/or the services offered through the Site.

## California Residents – Your Privacy Rights.

Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California can obtain certain information about the types of personal information that companies with whom they have an established business relationship have shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year. In particular, the law provides that companies must inform consumers about the categories of personal information that have been shared with third parties, the names and addresses of those third parties, and examples of the types of services or products marketed by those third parties. To request a copy of the information disclosure provided by SUCCESS pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, please contact us via the email address stated above. Please allow 30 days for a response.

## Binding Agreement; Changes.

Any user that accesses all or any part of this Site, or subscribes for newsletters or e-mail notifications and other information, or submits content to our Site for posting on the Site agrees and represents that such user is at least eighteen (18) years old and that such user has consented to this Privacy Policy. Each time a user accesses this Site, this Privacy Policy should be reviewed because SUCCESS reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time without prior notice. Your use of our Site constitutes your acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy.

## Links.

This Site may provide links to other web sites that SUCCESS thinks you will find interesting or useful. You may also link to these other web sites for a product or service featured on this Site. SUCCESS is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites, and you should review those policies.

## Disputes.

If you choose to visit our Site, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our [Terms of Use](https://privacy.www.success.com/terms-of-use/). By visiting the Site, using the services offered on the Site, or submitting and/or posting content to the Site, you agree that the laws of the State of Texas, without regard to principles of conflict of laws, will govern this Agreement and any dispute of any sort that might arise between you and us. Any dispute relating in any way to your visit to the Site, using the services offered on the Site and/or submitting and/or posting content on the Site, shall be adjudicated in any state court in Collin County, Texas, or any federal court in the Northern District of Texas and you and we consent to exclusive jurisdiction and venue in such courts and waive any and all claims of inconvenient forum and immunity. YOU AND WE EXPRESSLY AGREE HEREBY, TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW TO WAIVE THE RIGHT TO A TRIAL BY JURY.

Updated: May 2018
